<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout
xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
 xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
 xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
 android:layout_width="match_parent"
 android:layout_height="match_parent"
 android:background="@drawable/gavi2"
 tools:context=".MainActivity5">
 <TextView
 android:id="@+id/textView15"
 android:layout_width="362dp"
 android:layout_height="425dp"
 android:text="Gavi is an Eco-Tourism a project of the Kerala Forest
Development Corporation located in Pathanamthitta district, Kerala. Gavi,
located in Pathanamthitta district offers its visitors activities like
trekking, wildlife watching, outdoor camping in specially built tents, and
night safaris. Distance from Pathanamthitta To Gavi is 109 km 428 mtrs and
Travel Time is 2 hour 5 mins By Road. Gavi is 14 km south west of
Vandiperiyar, 28 km from Kumily, near Thekkady. Gavi is inside the Ranni
reserve forest. Gavi is a part of Seethathode Panchayath in Ranni Taluk.
Gavi is part of the Periyar Tiger Reserve, and the route can be covered by
car from Vandiperiyar. The entrance fee is 25 rupees per person and 50
rupees per vehicle. Cameras are 25 rupees and video cameras are charged 100
rupees. Both day and night stays are available. Forest tent camping is
available from November through March. It has been said that most
enjoyable route to Gavi is the way from Pathanamthitta. The rough journey
to Gavi may better be made on a sturdy vehicle like a jeep. Entry passes
must be obtained from the Forest Check Post en route at Vallakkadavu.
Advance booking with the Kerala Forest Development Corporation Ltd. is
highly appreciable wherein such formalities will be taken care of by the
company itself."
 android:textStyle="bold"
 app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
 app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
 app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="0.489"
 app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
 app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
 app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.313" />
 <Button
 android:id="@+id/button"
 android:layout_width="wrap_content"
 android:layout_height="wrap_content"
 android:text="Click Here for more"
 app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
 app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
 app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
 app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
 app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.748" />
</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>
